I've got it!
I got it!
Whoo!
Wow!
That was so much fun!
I'm having so much fun!
It's great to have the same hobbies!
It's really great!
It's great!
Yoo-hoo! I'm Shiho Kato from Hinatazaka46.
I'm Nao Kosaka.
Today, the two of us came to Universal Studios Japan.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
We're in the store before entering the park,
I've been told that here you can pick out goods that suit you and that you can wear,
I'd like to have them choose for me now.
I'm going.
I think today's outfit is chic,
How about this Snoopy zebra-print racquet hat?
I like it. At least.
Kitty. Below.
The brown one is a kitty.
Gal!
A very gal.
Wait a minute.
It's nice. Amazing.
It's really good.
Is she going to be okay? I'm getting worried.
It's really cute.
I really love hail patterns.
Really?
When I was in junior high school, I usually wore a hail pattern.
Isn't it similar?
Yes, I had a hail pattern.
I had a hail pattern. Hail pattern.
There was a hail pattern.
Here it is.
It's so cute.
The color of the catsuit matches the color of the clothes,
Indeed. Black with white.
I wonder if this is also an option.
I think it is also possible there.
I'm starting to have a hard time.
Then I'll go with this one.
Then let's both match with Snoopy.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Let's do it. Unifight.
We're in.
It's in.
It's good.
Great.
Fun.
What a sun, it's been a long time. Like this.
It's quite rare, isn't it? Like this.
Oh no. Oh no.
Amazing.
Ah, there's Yamayama-sensei's autograph.
I got it.
Look.
He signed it.
And Kanao-kun and Ai-chan's autographs too.
That's right.
On the shapeless side. Good luck.
I've only experienced solving Kageyama-san's riddles.
It's my first time.
The real one.
Let's go.
You sure you want to go with Hosher?
Yes, that's fine.
I'll go with that.
But I only called Shimo-san.
Hosher.
Guide map.
Oh, wow.
Wow, how many times are we going to do this with a big map?
Are you okay? Today.
I haven't woken up yet.
It's a big place.
Are you okay?
I haven't woken up yet.
It's still morning.
I wonder what kind of video we're going to get today.
I wonder what the video will be like.
But today we are going to keep it simple.But today we are going to keep it simple.
We have a YouTube shoot.
We just want to show you how we have fun.
We just want to show you that we are having fun.
We are just having fun.
That's right.
This is our third time.
We're going to do a lot together.
You don't seem to have much of an image as a band member.
You certainly don't give the impression of playing a lot in your private life, do you?
Yes, we do.
We are very much the same.
You were pretty bulletproof when you came here before, weren't you?
It's a step in the right direction.
I was furious.
I see.
She went along with my desire to go.
Nao-chan.
It's about to start again.
Hello!
Hello! Let's have fun together today!
I'm already excited!
Nashka's new facility at Interpol.
You said you want to work closely with the legend of Pacific Bree!
Wow!
Please gather slowly if you see the word "machine" in the Abraz!
Oh my god, it's starting.
I'm so excited I made it to the front of the line!
I'm really at the front of the line?
I'm really at the front of the pack...
I don't know, it's great, it's great, it's great, it's great!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Five seconds to go in Mission 1!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Five, four, three, two.
Mission 1 is about to begin.
Is this it?
Oh! Wait, it's minus, minus, minus.
I'm gonna have to go get it back.
I've got to get it back.
I'm right!
By all means, by all means, by all means.
How did you know?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, my God.
We're amazing.
Oh, no.
There's an emergency.
This music is bad.
The emergency exits are logged and the venue is not master keyed.
I will fight.
I ask that everyone remain where they are for a moment longer until safety is assured.
Everyone is solving the riddle. Oh, man.
What?
Brother Subaru.
Oh, it's from Ai-chan.
I'm so happy that Ai-chan sent me.
It's difficult.
It's over.
Buddy.
Uchira is really a great detective.
It was a lot of fun.
Was it much difficult?
It was much more difficult.
It was difficult, but it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun.
I can feel it.
Do Subaru.
Do the Subaru.
What's that?
It's so much fun.
Right?
Hey?
It made me fluffy.
I was moved.
I don't know how to say it, it's so linked to the movie.
I don't know how to say it, but it's connected to the film.
AI is connected to it.
And also computers.
Yes, yes.
I had never been here before,
I thought it was just a mystery-solving attraction,
I thought so too.
I was thinking that it was just about solving riddles,
I really enjoyed it,
I was like, "Wow!
It's pretty clear.
You got it?
Yes, I did. That's all I have to say,
Next,Next,
I've done well.
I'm off.
I'm going to have fun.
I love it so much.
Really?
I'm so happy.
It's a beautiful day.
I'm going to enjoy the attractions in the nice weather.
I'm going to enjoy.
I'm going.
Bye bye.
Here we go. Let's go to the world of the movie star!
By the way, everyone, on the movie...
Wait for me under 8:00.
What's up? Amity 3.
Amity 3.
Amity 3 is imminent.
I'm right near Toei.
Ripe, it's Ripe.
Dig the shark.
Yo-kai.
One more shot.
Oh, no.
That was good.
I've never seen it this close before.
Ten more minutes.
Then we'll all be samurai.
No way.
I don't want to take the bait.
It's hot.
I was so surprised I hit the gas pop.
That feels good.
A little tease for Marinami.
Marina Mi.
Chocolate.
Hold on.
I'm here, I'm here.
Yes, I'm here. Good idea to me.
Let's play this game ramp.
This time I'll do it.
I'm on it.
Let's see who wins.
Whoo!
Win!
That was fun.
This, you know, normal stuff,
Walking around...
It's quite rare.
No, it's quite rare. Isn't it fun?
Wow! Wow, so many!
The music is great, too, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Wow!
Flying Dinosaur!
I'm going to go for a ride.
I can't usually scream.
I want to scream.
I'm off.
How do you choose?
I'm going to fly.
Oh, no. Now?
Aah!
Oh, no!
Bye-bye.
Thank you for watching!
Did you enjoy The Flying Dynas, presented by JCB?
It's fun!
Oh my God!
It was fun!
Ha-ha-ha!
Oh no!
If you yell in the street or something...If you yell in the street or something...
If you yell in the street...
They'll chase you down.
I usually scream in places like this.
You're right.
Nao-chan was yelling a lot, too.
I did a lot of yelling.
At times like this, you have to scream.
That's right.
And I like to relax at the end of the ride.
Today, when I was relaxing...
But you know what?
Of course, I told the people in line that she's hot.
Wow, this is fun!
I don't know...
Oh my God!
Why doesn't her hair fall out?
It's really bad.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Even after the Flying Dinosaur ride, my bangs look like this.
I think I could probably break some kind of record for that one.
I'll prove it right here on YouTube.
I don't know what it is.
We're going to go back to our favorite
We're going to our favorite place.
We're going.
We have surprisingly similar interests.
We have similar interests.
Yes, so maybe that's why we get along so well.
Yes.
Our personalities are surprisingly opposite.
Surprisingly opposite.
But our hobbies are very similar.
Yes, our hobbies are very similar.
This way, this way.
Can you see it?
Dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum
Dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum dum.
Hey, over there.
I'm excited just to be here.
I'm already excited.
Oh, man.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Oh, no, no, no, no!
I'm gonna cry.
We're dressed now.
Yay!
We actually had a meeting, didn't we?
We did.
I'm Griffindor.
I'm Sleeder.
Surprising.
Oh my God!
Oh, no... Oh, no... Oh, no...
There's a lot of the same dormmates. We've been slipping around a lot.
We've been slipping a lot.
Then we're going to Three Broomsticks.
We're on three brooms.
We're going to have lunch.
We're going to have lunch
Wow, that's a lot of food. But I've actually eaten quite a bit.
Oh, really?
I'm really a regular.
That's what I'd expect.
I'd love to have a Butterbeer. Butter beer.
Butterbeer sounds good.
I want to drink butter beer.
Oh, really. We have rose butter beer. You just said that.
It's my first time drinking Rose Butter Beer.
It's my first time, too.
I guess I haven't been here much in the summer. Me.
Oh, I don't anyway.
Niversal Studios Japan.
Is it on?
In a scary house.
How long have you liked Harry Potter?
Harry Potter in elementary school.
But Hon-nan was earlier.
I've loved it since I was in middle school.
Harry Potter in upper elementary school.
About the same.
I got into it when I was...
When I was in elementary school.
There was a book in the school library.
The book type.
I started with books.
I have a unique imagination.
I wrote about a secret room.
I was in the sixth grade, I think.I think I was in sixth grade.
That's amazing.
I had a school bag and a hand-me-down bag every day.
I always had heavy books in my hand-me-down bag.
The kind my mother would make for me.
That's right.
The smallest elementary schooler you can imagine.
And every year we had movies with subtitles.
And the regular dubbed ones.
He watches them all over again.
I can't believe it.
But you know what taught me how to watch them?
Mom.
It's interesting to watch them both.
It's a totally different way of interpreting a role.
I don't know...
This isn't fun.
In the afterglow.
It's all about the afterglow.
We can talk about it all the time.
It's great to have the same hobbies.
It's really great.
It's great.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
It's true, Frozen.
There it is.
Oh, wow.
I've never had frozen butter beer before.
I wonder if I can drink it.
Bon appétit.
Yes, sir.
Are you drinking?
Drink up, drink up, drink up. - No?
I'll go back for my beard.
Oh, it's on.
It's on.
Oh, my God.
Straw gun.
I didn't realize you had a straw gun.
Oh, my God.
Hold on.
Oh, that's goo.
Oh, wow.
That's a meat pie.
Oh, it's a Hogwarts.
It's got an "H" on it.
H for Hogwarts.
That's what you wanted, right?
I don't know.
It's good.
It's so good.
Oh, my gosh.
Meat
Meat-meat.
Yum!
Meat Meat
Yum.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's huge.
It looks so good.
It's bigger than it looks in the picture.
They're, um... bigger.
Where do I start?
Bon appétit!
Wow, it's pretty filling.
Yes, it's very filling.
That's a good sign!
Gooo!
Umamama coffee change.
Um-um coffee change?
Umay!
Fishy!
Fish good?
Am I supposed to be enjoying this?
Just enjoy it.
Have fun.
Oh, I forgot.
I'm going to try this one more time after I eat this.
I'm going to try again.
I'm so happy!
Happy mambo
Uma mama mama mama mama mama mama mama mama
what is that?What's that?
You mentioned it earlier.
I don't know what it is.
I've been saying it since I was in high school.
I've been saying it since high school.
What?
"Uma-omenon hihiin.
Didn't you just make that?
No, I didn't.
You know, with the second-term opposition...
I...
I've been friends with Nao-chan for quite a while.
But Suzu-chan and Hina...
There's been a lot of them lately.
I'm getting to talk with the other second-term students.
I thought I could talk with them.
You've been together for about seven years now.
That's right.
I was like...
I wondered how long it's taken you to get to know each other.
But I guess that's just how it is.
Time is of the essence, isn't it?
Time is the key.
Yes, yes, yes.
You know, the fourth-term students, they just joined us recently.
They don't talk much.
But I get along well with Konishi.
I can talk with Konishi because we get along well.
I feel like we get along really well.
You get Haccho, don't you?
I do think we're a little alike.
Really? What's the vibe? Atmosphere?
Atmosphere.
I'm glad.
I can feel your love for Shigosan.
I can tell that you really like him.
In which moment?
It's all coming out.
Oh, really?
The way you talk with Shigo...
I'm glad I'm so insensitive.
You talked with Mr. Shigo quite a while later, didn't you?
Yes, we thought about it for a while.
A lot of time.
We needed a period of time.
It took time.
I wonder how long.
Isn't it Dasada?
We got to know each other at Dassada.
How long did it take?
Nineteen years, twenty years, something like that.
How long have you been friends?
We started talking a lot.
You were close in position.
Yes, we were.
That's one of the reasons.
It takes a few years, right?
It will.
We're a shy duo.
Now we'll see where we go.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I can see it, I can see it, I can see it.
Oh, no!
Oh, here it comes!
Oita
Oh, my God!
I thought so... I thought so...
Oh, man...
My heart is just dancing
My heart is dancing
I'm dancing my heart out
Don't think about tomorrow
Don't think about now
Yes, don't think about tomorrow
Don't think about it now. It was fun.
It was so much fun. It was great.
It was great. It's been a while since I've been on one of these.
It's been a while since I've been on one of these, but when the dementors attacked us.
When the dementors attacked us.
Harry said...
Harry was like, "Stay with me.
He's so handsome. He's so cool.
I love him. I love him so much.
I'll never leave you.
He's really good-looking.
He's out there.
I got away from Harry.
Thank you, Harry.Thank you Harry.
I love you.
I'll be back.
Bye-bye.
My favorite.
I'm going to the attraction.
Soon.
It's going to close soon.
About the fun.
Might be the last one.
Wow.
Spiderman!
Cool, I love it!
Watch out!
Mr. A is so smooth!
He's so cool.
I'm getting blown up.
Watch out!
Look out!
Please stop!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh, no. Oh, no.
High, high, high.
I don't want to fall.
It's not safe.
I don't want to.
Stop! Stop! Stop!
Oh, my God!
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Thank you. Thank you.
Spider-Man!
I love it!
I went on the Spiderman ride.
That was fun.
It was more intense than I remember.
It was so much fun.
Here's the ending.
I'm sorry.
This was the last one.
Thank you very much.
How was it?
It was a lot of fun.
We usually have a lot of fun and relax.
But today we were active.
I got to ride all kinds of rides.
It was a great day!
It was a day full of breath!
I'm glad we had a nice dinner.
I'm glad we did.
It's been a long time since we've had so much fun.
It was a lot of fun.
And we got to soak up some sun.
It was also a lot of fun to be here with you, Shiho.
Thank you very much.
Let's go somewhere again!
Let's go again!
Thank you for watching!
Subscribe to our channel
Please give us a high rating!
Bye bye!
Next Episode
Meteorozincs
Huh? You're hurting me.
Let's go again.
It's a little sad.
Not yet.
Meteorozincs.
Wow!
That's great!
I did it, I did it!
Aguamenti.
There it is!
Aguamenti
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God!
I got a big one!